The 4th day of the rehearsal of the 41st single, Under Live, by Nogizaka46.
On this day, the 6th grade students were performing a new song.
What were they practicing on this day?
The 22nd single, the under song, Nichijou, was released in 2018.
The first center was the 2nd generation student, Hinako Kitano.
After this song, the center continued to perform under live.
Documentary of 41stSG Under Live ~ A different view from the 6th generation ~ Part 2 of 3
The 6th grade students performed this song for the first time under live.
What does this song mean?
This is the opinion of the original member Iwamoto
After the song, Under Live, became a symbol of the members.
I thought it was a song that symbolized the members.
When I see the members dancing this song.
I feel that they are standing on the stage with various emotions.
I also feel that I'm hiding in myself.
I also perform while hitting the feelings that I don't reveal.
I think it's a song that really resembles the members.
I am treasuring it.
A song with great meaning in the history of Under Live.
Nichijou (Every Day).
Under Live has changed more and more.
It's not the song I used to play at Under Live.
It's not like that, but I try to put in some recent songs
But I feel like I'm at the center of Nichijou because I'm connected to it without any interruptions.
After the full performance, the individual performances began.
At the end of the performance, the seniors began to look at the situation from behind.
The difference in the choreography is not the skill, but the details.
It's been a long time since I've done this.
The lessons with the seniors begin.
The more it goes, the more kind they are.
It's hard to say, but I'm really free to do the whole song.
I'm free every time before rehearsal, and I do rehearsals with the seniors.
When I do it with the seniors, I'm a little nervous, and I think there's more to it than just motivation, so I think it's hard.
I don't know if it's because I have a lot of motivation that it's a little easier to do.
As Shibata said, 10 of the 6th gen students are more than half of the whole team.
That's why this time, Nichojou will be a special performance.
That's what I'm going to do with my Nichijou impressions, so I'm going to do it with the seniors.
I'm going to do it cool together, but I don't think I'm going to lose to them.
I think I have the feeling that I'm going to win.
The excitement and excitement for the live performance made by new members.
The rehearsal continues.
Shibata, who is a 4th grader, is celebrating her birthday on this day.
Happy birthday!
One page of peaceful rehearsals.
Kind seniors, strong colleagues.
The rehearsal was supposed to go smoothly.
From the beginning, the seniors were too fast and too good.
I feel like I'm being left behind and I'm in a hurry.
I think I'm going to be a punk.
This is the continuation of every day.
Until the end of the set list rehearsal.
Next time, live every day.
The tall wall that stood in front of me.